[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Farrah", "Tatum"]}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Piers Morgan, are you?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "Morgan", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "Tonight he's back talking candidly and emotionally about Farrah, Tatum and his other children, and his own battle with cancer.", "answer_tokens": ["Tonight", "he", "'s", "back", "talking", "candidly", "and", "emotionally", "about", "Farrah", ",", "Tatum", "and", "his", "other", "children", ",", "and", "his", "own", "battle", "with", "cancer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Morgan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Did you conclude that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "conclude", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "I feel that I failed Farrah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "that", "I", "failed", "Farrah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Is that a fair allegation, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "fair", "allegation", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, I don't know if I'm qualified to judge politics, but I think there is a kind of convergence here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "'m", "qualified", "to", "judge", "politics", ",", "but", "I", "think", "there", "is", "a", "kind", "of", "convergence", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "From what you saw and witnessed ground, what would you say?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "saw", "and", "witnessed", "ground", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well, it certainly was not covert.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "certainly", "was", "not", "covert", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "And in a sense, if they don't, then the original point of this war, to go in, yes, to take on al Qaeda but also to take on the Taliban, who are protecting the al Qaeda operatives, if that fails, if the Taliban simply revert to the way they were before, and there is a genuine fear they do that, then the overall gambit, if you like, of the war would have failed, won't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "a", "sense", ",", "if", "they", "do", "n't", ",", "then", "the", "original", "point", "of", "this", "war", ",", "to", "go", "in", ",", "yes", ",", "to", "take", "on", "al", "Qaeda", "but", "also", "to", "take", "on", "the", "Taliban", ",", "who", "are", "protecting", "the", "al", "Qaeda", "operatives", ",", "if", "that", "fails", ",", "if", "the", "Taliban", "simply", "revert", "to", "the", "way", "they", "were", "before", ",", "and", "there", "is", "a", "genuine", "fear", "they", "do", "that", ",", "then", "the", "overall", "gambit", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "of", "the", "war", "would", "have", "failed", ",", "wo", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Well, you know, it depends on what we feel is a failure.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "depends", "on", "what", "we", "feel", "is", "a", "failure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Taliban"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "So in the first instance I was really shocked and I said, oh my god, what is it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "in", "the", "first", "instance", "I", "was", "really", "shocked", "and", "I", "said", ",", "oh", "my", "god", ",", "what", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Freaky, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Freaky", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "And who went to see who first?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "went", "to", "see", "who", "first", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I went to see him first.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "went", "to", "see", "him", "first", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "In Chicago?", "question_tokens": ["In", "Chicago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "In Chicago.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "Chicago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "What did he cook you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "cook", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "He cooked me Indonesian food on that day.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "cooked", "me", "Indonesian", "food", "on", "that", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Any good?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "It was really good, it was really good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "really", "good", ",", "it", "was", "really", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Did you feel a brother-sister thing?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "a", "brother-sister", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "What did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "It was a moment of great pride because, you know, I was so proud of him.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "moment", "of", "great", "pride", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "was", "so", "proud", "of", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Did you approve of your brother's choice of bride?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "approve", "of", "your", "brother", "'s", "choice", "of", "bride", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Definitely, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Do you remember what you said to him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "what", "you", "said", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I said well done, little brother, well done.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "well", "done", ",", "little", "brother", ",", "well", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Not much more to say, really, is there?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "much", "more", "to", "say", ",", "really", ",", "is", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "RBR", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "No, no, because he's always my brother and he remains my brother.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "because", "he", "'s", "always", "my", "brother", "and", "he", "remains", "my", "brother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Can you speak to him if he's president much?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "speak", "to", "him", "if", "he", "'s", "president", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "As much as you speak to your sibling, your brother or your sister, depending on what your work, you know, your time allows.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "much", "as", "you", "speak", "to", "your", "sibling", ",", "your", "brother", "or", "your", "sister", ",", "depending", "on", "what", "your", "work", ",", "you", "know", ",", "your", "time", "allows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Is it that easy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "that", "easy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "What, he picks the phone up?", "question_tokens": ["What", ",", "he", "picks", "the", "phone", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Look, you can call the White House, there's a number.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "you", "can", "call", "the", "White", "House", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "number", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 231, "question": "You must have been there a few times, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "have", "been", "there", "a", "few", "times", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Yes, I --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Do you sometimes say to him, look, mate, you're my brother and here's my advice on this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "sometimes", "say", "to", "him", ",", "look", ",", "mate", ",", "you", "'re", "my", "brother", "and", "here", "'s", "my", "advice", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "You know, the thing is, he has such a particular job to do, and I do a certain kind of job myself.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "thing", "is", ",", "he", "has", "such", "a", "particular", "job", "to", "do", ",", "and", "I", "do", "a", "certain", "kind", "of", "job", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "What does your sister do, what is her job?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "your", "sister", "do", ",", "what", "is", "her", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "She's a mother of four children.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "a", "mother", "of", "four", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Did you hear that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "hear", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I did, I heard it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", ",", "I", "heard", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "At Christmas parties, does he do the Al Green impression?", "question_tokens": ["At", "Christmas", "parties", ",", "does", "he", "do", "the", "Al", "Green", "impression", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I heard it the first time when he did it on TV.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "heard", "it", "the", "first", "time", "when", "he", "did", "it", "on", "TV", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Did you know he had a good voice?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "he", "had", "a", "good", "voice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "No, my brother has a sense of humor.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "my", "brother", "has", "a", "sense", "of", "humor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "It's an amazing story, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "amazing", "story", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What is it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yes, there is a Web site.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "there", "is", "a", "Web", "site", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Fine.", "answer_tokens": ["Fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "How are things now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "things", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Quite good, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Quite", "good", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "ORGAN: Was that helpful or not, doing that show?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Was", "that", "helpful", "or", "not", ",", "doing", "that", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I don't think it was very helpful, no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "was", "very", "helpful", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "In what way?", "question_tokens": ["In", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Well, they said you're against him, remember that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "said", "you", "'re", "against", "him", ",", "remember", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "You think from the start the premise was never going to work for you two?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "from", "the", "start", "the", "premise", "was", "never", "going", "to", "work", "for", "you", "two", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Well, we thought we had a plan, she and I, in that we would make stuff up.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "thought", "we", "had", "a", "plan", ",", "she", "and", "I", ",", "in", "that", "we", "would", "make", "stuff", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "So what is the prognosis for you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "is", "the", "prognosis", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Well, I don't plan to give in to it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "plan", "to", "give", "in", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "'NEAL: To the story?", "question_tokens": ["'NEAL", ":", "To", "the", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Yes, this is your life generally.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "this", "is", "your", "life", "generally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "How's he doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "'s", "he", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "He's -- he hasn't read it.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "--", "he", "has", "n't", "read", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "You have no contact with him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "no", "contact", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Do you feel, when you read the book back and you read all this stuff and relived it all -- do you feel you gave parenting your best shot or do you think that you were too selfish, perhaps, at times?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", ",", "when", "you", "read", "the", "book", "back", "and", "you", "read", "all", "this", "stuff", "and", "relived", "it", "all", "--", "do", "you", "feel", "you", "gave", "parenting", "your", "best", "shot", "or", "do", "you", "think", "that", "you", "were", "too", "selfish", ",", "perhaps", ",", "at", "times", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I know I tried.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "know", "I", "tried", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Did you try hard enough?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "try", "hard", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I don't know about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Did you conclude that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "conclude", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I feel that I failed Farrah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "that", "I", "failed", "Farrah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Do you regret that now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "that", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "But do you think you're capable of ever loving like that again?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "capable", "of", "ever", "loving", "like", "that", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Only her.", "answer_tokens": ["Only", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Did you ever hit her inappropriately, now that you look back at it?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "hit", "her", "inappropriately", ",", "now", "that", "you", "look", "back", "at", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Well, I missed her inappropriately.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "missed", "her", "inappropriately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Did you ever try and punch her?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "try", "and", "punch", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "I -- she went into a bathroom and I punched the door and the door collapsed and hit her in the eye and I broke my hand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "she", "went", "into", "a", "bathroom", "and", "I", "punched", "the", "door", "and", "the", "door", "collapsed", "and", "hit", "her", "in", "the", "eye", "and", "I", "broke", "my", "hand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "-- a pretty chaotic world, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["--", "a", "pretty", "chaotic", "world", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "He was -- he was exposed to two people who loved each other very much, and was confused by what was happening now.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "--", "he", "was", "exposed", "to", "two", "people", "who", "loved", "each", "other", "very", "much", ",", "and", "was", "confused", "by", "what", "was", "happening", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What do you think of what she says there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "what", "she", "says", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I think she's saying a -- a smart thing, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'s", "saying", "a", "--", "a", "smart", "thing", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "I mean when you -- when you said, oh, what's the other one called, how did you feel after you -- you said that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "when", "you", "--", "when", "you", "said", ",", "oh", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "other", "one", "called", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "after", "you", "--", "you", "said", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "What -- I don't know what you mean.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "you", "mean", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "I mean you've written a book about them, so I guess it's fair to ask, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "you", "'ve", "written", "a", "book", "about", "them", ",", "so", "I", "guess", "it", "'s", "fair", "to", "ask", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Well, I thought I was writing about Farrah, but -- but they were around.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "I", "was", "writing", "about", "Farrah", ",", "but", "--", "but", "they", "were", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 591, "question": "I fueled the circus?", "question_tokens": ["I", "fueled", "the", "circus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "No, do you think you fuel -- continue to fuel the circus, when, if you write a book about all the trials and tribulations --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "fuel", "--", "continue", "to", "fuel", "the", "circus", ",", "when", ",", "if", "you", "write", "a", "book", "about", "all", "the", "trials", "and", "tribulations", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "You don't feel you have to go down and get a license?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "feel", "you", "have", "to", "go", "down", "and", "get", "a", "license", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "No, I -- I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "As well as I can.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "well", "as", "I", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "I mean, do you think you ever will be able to?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "ever", "will", "be", "able", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 636, "question": "Let go of my home?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "go", "of", "my", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "No, or either the home or the memory of Farrah --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "or", "either", "the", "home", "or", "the", "memory", "of", "Farrah", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "In that moment, how did you feel, when she realized what you were doing?", "question_tokens": ["In", "that", "moment", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", ",", "when", "she", "realized", "what", "you", "were", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "It's the kind of scene that is in films.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "kind", "of", "scene", "that", "is", "in", "films", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Redmond"]}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "The moment you knew you'd lost her, that she'd gone, obviously, you were grief-stricken, but what did you think would happen to the rest of your life without Farrah anymore, given how young she was, comparatively?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "you", "knew", "you", "'d", "lost", "her", ",", "that", "she", "'d", "gone", ",", "obviously", ",", "you", "were", "grief-stricken", ",", "but", "what", "did", "you", "think", "would", "happen", "to", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "without", "Farrah", "anymore", ",", "given", "how", "young", "she", "was", ",", "comparatively", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Well, my thoughts were for Redmond, because he was in jail and he didn't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "thoughts", "were", "for", "Redmond", ",", "because", "he", "was", "in", "jail", "and", "he", "did", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "What does he make of you as a dad, do you think, now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "he", "make", "of", "you", "as", "a", "dad", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "He likes me.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "likes", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "I mean in an ideal world, how would you see it mapping out?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "in", "an", "ideal", "world", ",", "how", "would", "you", "see", "it", "mapping", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "I -- I don't think about it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Do you see making movies as part of that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "making", "movies", "as", "part", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "No --", "answer_tokens": ["No", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120502pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]